Your products are one of the most important parts
of your advertising campaigns, which
is why we created a products page that helps you monitor
the ad performance metrics of your advertised products,
and provides relevant recommendations
from Amazon Ads that you can implement.
The products page is located at the campaign manager
with the Amazon ad console.
On the products page, you can monitor performance metrics,
impressions, clicks, and ad-attributed sales,
and find recommended tips and actionable insights
to help improve your product listings.
For products with associated Sponsored Products
and sponsored display campaigns, you
can expand the product level performance to the campaign
and ad group levels to view more details.
You can also create new campaigns with selected ASINs,
or add products directly to existing campaigns and ad groups.
Check out the products page to help save time
reviewing your product performance and recommendations
all in one place.